bravelets.com 2019-07-09

# BRAVELETS PRIVACY POLICY – Bravelets

Last Modified: October 2013

**Our Commitment to Privacy **

We at Bravelets, LLC ( "We" or the "Company") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit bravelets.com (our "Website" ) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect on this Website and in e-mail and other electronic messages between you and this Website. It does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website (whether operated by the Company or any third party), or any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy, below). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**What kind of information does Bravelets collect? **

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:

information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number (“personal information”);

information that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as the items in your shopping cart; and/or

information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information directly from you when you provide it to us and automatically as you navigate through the site, as described below.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**How do we use cookies and other tracking technologies? **

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information, using cookies and other tracking technologies, about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including details of your visits to our Website and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. The information we collect automatically is statistical data, and does not identify you individually. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service to you.

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of our Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

**How does Bravelets use my information? **

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

To present our Website and its contents to you.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.

To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.

To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.

To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.

In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

We may also use your information to contact you about our goods and services, and information about our charitable causes, that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data.

**Does Bravelets share my information? **

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.

To a buyer or other successor in the unlikely event of a sale or merger of our business, in which personal information held by us about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

We may also disclose your personal information:

To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

To enforce or apply our Terms of Use _www.bravelets.com/website-terms_ and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Bravelets, LLC, our customers or others.

**How do I access or change my information? **

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an e-mail at info@bravelets.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use _www.bravelets.com/website-terms_

**How do I know my personal information is secure? **

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions are encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**How does Bravelets protect kids’ privacy? **

We are concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the internet. Our Website is not targeted to or intended for use by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at _[info@bravelets.com](mailto:info@bravelets.com)_ or Bravelets, 337 Garden Oaks Blvd #46624, Houston, TX 77018, Attn: Bravelets Legal.

**Your California Privacy Rights **

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to _[info@bravelets.com](mailto:info@bravelets.com)_ or write us at: Bravelets, 337 Garden Oaks Blvd #46624, Houston, TX 77018, Attn: Bravelets Legal.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy **

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information **

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Email: _[info@bravelets.com](mailto:info@bravelets.com)_

Address:

Attn: Bravelets Legal

337 Garden Oaks Blvd #46624, Houston, TX 77018

Houston, TX 77018
